[
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticInstructionsState_01",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+3=",
            "solution": 5
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "AdditionPractice",
    "type": "ArithmeticPracticeState",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+3=",
            "solution": 5
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticPracticeState",
    "name": "AdditionPractice",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+9=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+8=",
            "solution": 17
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticPracticeFinishedState_return",
    "desc_head": "SymbolicNumberComparison_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "SymbolicNumberComparison_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [
        {
          "name": "TaskHandler",
          "params": {
            "num_left": "1",
            "num_right": "2",
            "solution": 2,
            "distance": 1
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticState",
    "name": "Addition",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+3=",
            "solution": 5
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+4=",
            "solution": 6
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+5=",
            "solution": 7
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+6=",
            "solution": 8
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+7=",
            "solution": 9
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+8=",
            "solution": 10
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "2+9=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+2=",
            "solution": 5
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+4=",
            "solution": 7
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+5=",
            "solution": 8
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+6=",
            "solution": 9
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+7=",
            "solution": 10
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+8=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "3+9=",
            "solution": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+2=",
            "solution": 6
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+3=",
            "solution": 7
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+5=",
            "solution": 9
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+6=",
            "solution": 10
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+7=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+8=",
            "solution": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "4+9=",
            "solution": 13
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+2=",
            "solution": 7
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+3=",
            "solution": 8
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+4=",
            "solution": 9
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+6=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+7=",
            "solution": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+8=",
            "solution": 13
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "5+9=",
            "solution": 14
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+2=",
            "solution": 8
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+3=",
            "solution": 9
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+4=",
            "solution": 10
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+5=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+7=",
            "solution": 13
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+8=",
            "solution": 14
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "6+9=",
            "solution": 15
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+2=",
            "solution": 9
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+3=",
            "solution": 10
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+4=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+5=",
            "solution": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+6=",
            "solution": 13
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+8=",
            "solution": 15
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "7+9=",
            "solution": 16
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+2=",
            "solution": 10
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+3=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+4=",
            "solution": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+5=",
            "solution": 13
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+6=",
            "solution": 14
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+7=",
            "solution": 15
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "8+9=",
            "solution": 17
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+2=",
            "solution": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+3=",
            "solution": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+4=",
            "solution": 13
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+5=",
            "solution": 14
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+6=",
            "solution": 15
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+7=",
            "solution": 16
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "9+8=",
            "solution": 17
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
	{ "name": "TaskDoneState", "type": "TaskDoneState", "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD", "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY", "done": false, "saved": false, "trials": [ ] },
  {
    "type": "SAVE",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false
  },
  {
    "type": "REDIRECT",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "to": {
      "type": "LevelSelectState"
    }
  }
]